ARSENII PEREVERTAILO SOFTWARE DEVELOPER

arsenii-perevertailo.com I linkedin.com/in/arskgg I github.com/arskgg I arsenyper@gmail.com

Purposeful, communicable and responsible full-stack developer who is always willing to improve. Have web application hosting experience, knowledge of fundamental design patterns and development practices, SDLC principle, Scrum and Kanban methodologies, algorithms and data structures.

TECHNICAL SKILLS

Front-end: JavaScript, React.js, Next.js, Vue.js, Redux/RTK Query, HTML, CSS (SASS), Tailwind, Bootstrap, Quasar, Material-UI, Framer Motion

Back-end: Node.js, Express.js, REST API, NoSQL/SQL databases (Mongo DB), Mongoose, JWT

Tools & Technologies: NPM, Git/GitHub, UI/UX Design (Figma)

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

METOPIO I Chicago, IL

Contractor Front-end Developer | November 2022 - Present

- · Developing responsive web pages and reusable components using Vue.js and Quasar frameworks.
- Collaborate with a team of developers to resolve front-end issues.
- Analyzed UI/UX design for responsive layout and improved usability.
- · Turned designs and wireframes into web pages and specific reusable components.
- Converting client-provided data into table.
- Worked with API.
- · Code refactoring and bug fixes.

Tech Stack: Vue.is, Quasar, Pinia, TypeScript, Git/GitHub

FEATURED PROJECTS

GARAGE I social-garage.vercel.app

- · Created a full-stack social media application utilizing React.js on client side and Node.js on backend, hosted via Vercel.
- · Created database schemas. Designed and developed REST APIs to connect to the database.
- Implemented signup and login logic with access and refresh tokens using JWT library and storing them into cookies.
- · Created middleware for token validation and error handling.
- · Used RTK Query to send requests to the server.

Tech Stack: MERN, Redux/RTK, JWT, Material-UI, Framer Motion

GitHub: github.com/Arskgg/Garge_client, github.com/Arskgg/Garage_server

RELEVANT EXPERIENCE

Android Development

• Created, deployed, and maintained Android applications including Delivery app, Chat App, Food Tracker and more. **Key technologies:** Java, Kotlin, Android Jetpack, MVVM, SQL, Firebase, Google Play Connect, AdMob, XML, UI Design.

ADDITIONAL EXPERIENCE

H2H Movers Inc. | Chicago, IL

Team Lead | October 2020 - August 2022

Lead a team of 4-9 movers ensuring a smooth workflow by coordinating work, resolving queries and maintaining a high standard of communication. Managed finances and negotiated service prices and other fees with customers.

Trained new employees on safety and moving techniques.

EDUCATION

Software Engineering | October 2017 - October 2019

Warsaw School of Information Technology I Warsaw, Poland

Fields of study: Algorithms and Data Structures, Further Maths, Statistics, OOP, Relational Database, SQL, C/C++, C#, Java, JavaScript, PHP, HTML/CSS, XML and more.

LANGUAGES